I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
What I have to say has been
uttered in situations like this for ages.
昔からこういう場面でよく使う言葉をあなたに贈るわ
If "sorry" was enough, then we
wouldn't need the police, right?
ごめんで済んだら 警察はいらないんじゃない
After all that fuss, Talisman, the very
man you were after, got away.
あれだけ大騒ぎしておいて結局 本命のタリスマンは逃亡
Man, I never should've
cooperated with the police.
本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった
But there's no doubt that Talisman has
gotten caught up in some sort of crime.
でもね　タリスマンが犯罪に巻き込まれているのは間違いないの
You helped us because you felt
you couldn't just ignore that, right?
あなただってそれを見過ごせないと思ったから手伝ってくれたんでしょ
Give me a break!
I'm Spooky Boogie the anarchist!
いいかげんにして 私はスプーキーブーギー·ザ·アナーキー
Under no circumstance will
I ever act as your agent again.
もうどんなことがあろうと　金輪際 あなたたちの手先にはならないわ
But...
そんな…
Did it put a crack in your friendship?
友情にヒビ入れちゃったかしら
Well, she was just
someone from the same class.
でも　そもそも同級生ってだけで 誰なのかまでは分からないし
I don't even know who she is, so...
You recorded that chat, right?
今のチャットはログを取ってあるな
What?
えっ　そりゃもちろん
Yeah, of course.
My head is overflowing with thoughts
I can't allow anyone to know about
I've strayed into a world void of even mistakes
It's being rubbed in so deep it's hard to believe
This "world" that holds
only what the eye can see
Can I flush out the truth?
Plastic Tac Tic,
no one can go crazy anymore
You, too, are in a plastic beautiful world
In a world with too much beauty,
for some reason I can't see the light
My bursting heart is an eternal reflection
Secret remains for you
Don't expose these false colors and futures
fake's plastic world
keep it secret motion
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 西西   校对:西西   后期:时末
Talisman Saloon is packed
with visitors as usual.
#05  Nobody Knows Your Face
Today is another busy day
タリスマン·サルーンは相変わらず千客万来
for the ghost of Kimihiko Hayama,
giving out advice without a care.
葉山公彦の幽霊は今日ものうのうと人生相談に大忙しと
Not only is he not running or hiding,
逃げも隠れもしないどころか
he even brings up
what happened in Club Exoset.
クラブエグゾゼの件 ネタにしてるありさまですよ
More importantly,
just what is his game here?
そもそも こいつは何がしたいんだ
Is his goal to make it look
like Kimihiko Hayama is still alive?
葉山公彦が生きているように見せ掛けるのが目的なのか
Then there's no way he'd leave
Hayama's bank account untouched
だったら 銀行口座や外出記録を２カ月ほっとくわけがないでしょ
along with that record of him not
leaving his apartment for two months, right?
I wonder if his goal really is
simply to hijack Hayama's avatar.
やっぱり アバターをのっとるのだけが目的なんすかね
If he commits crimes
just for kicks, it's possible, but...
愉快犯と考えればあり得るが
would someone like that kill?
そのために殺人まで犯すか
Gino, don't try to understand the
mind of criminals. You'll be taken in.
ギノ　犯罪者の心理を理解しようとするな
のみ込まれるぞ
フンッ　それは貴様自身に対する戒めか　狡噛
Is that a warning to yourself, Kogami?
Hey...
おい…
Even if he commits
crimes for kicks, he's no fool.
やつは愉快犯だったとしてもバカじゃない
He expected that he'd fall under suspicion.
自分に嫌疑が掛かると予測していた
He couldn't have cracked
the Holo-Cosplay in the hall
会場全員のホロコスをクラッキングするなんて
unless he prepared for it beforehand.
事前の準備がなけりゃ無理な相談だ
If he's mocking us, then we'll
just have to teach him a lesson.
こちらをなめて掛かっているなら 思い知らせてやるまでだ
Karanomori, trace Talisman's access routes.
唐之杜　タリスマンのアクセスルートを追跡しろ
We'll find out who he is
and capture him this time for sure.
今度こそ身元を突き止めて押さえる
Don't get worked up, Gino.
熱くなるな　ギノ
He's supremely confident
in his ability to hide his tracks.
やつは逆探知対策に鉄壁の自信を持ってる
That's why he still goes in and out of
だからこそ　今でも平然とソーシャルネットに出入りしてるんだ
the social networks like nothing happened.
But what's the point in us
sitting around doing nothing?
ここで手をこまねいて何になる
There might be another way
to get a lead on him.
別の方法でやつの尻尾をつかめるかもしれない
There's one more
thing that I wanna check into.
まだ一つ　気になる件がある
That's fine. Suit yourself.
I'm still going to trace his access routes.
いいだろう　好きにしろ
俺は俺で　逆探知の線で進める
I can't really figure out
stuff like avatars and virtual worlds.
こういうアバターとかバーチャルとか
俺にはいまいち理解できん
I mean, after all, it's our bodies that
actually breathe, sweat, and eat, right?
息をして汗をかいて 飯を食うのは結局この体だろう
Mr. Masaoka, I think people
like you are an endangered species.
征陸さんみたいな人　今では絶滅危惧種だと思いますよ
Isn't using the net just
like using knives for cooking
ネットって物を調理するための刃物とか 記録するための紙とか
or using paper to write things down?
It has nothing to do with good or bad.
そういうレベルのものじゃないですかね
いい　悪いじゃない
It's like, it's there
so we accept it and use it.
そこにあるんだから受け入れる 「使う」っていう…
As expected, you're good at
explaining things. You're like a teacher.
さすがに 説明がうまいな
教師みたいだ
Really?
そうですか
Do you know Rousseau?
ルソーって知ってるか
Uhm, you mean the philosopher?
えっと…　哲学者の
Yeah. And his work
A Discourse on Inequality.
そう その著作の『人類不平等起源論』
Hold on a second, please. I'll look it up.
ちょっと待ってください 検索してみるんで
You don't need to. It's recorded in my brain.
その必要はない
俺の脳内には記憶されてる
For example, suppose there
are two hunters in a forest.
例えば ２人のハンターが森にいる
Should they hunt for rabbits separately?
それぞれ別々にウサギを狩るのか
Or...
それとも
...should they work together
and go after bigger prey?
２人で協力して大物を狙うか
Which decision do you think is correct?
どちらが正しい判断だと思う
Of course, the latter is.
もちろん後者です
That's the basics of game theory.
You work together to catch bigger prey.
ゲーム理論の基本
協力して大物
That's right. Humans are social by nature.
そのとおり それが人間の社会性だ
Languages, letters, currencies, telephones...
言葉　手紙　通貨　電話
All the communication
tools that exist in the world
この世に存在するありとあらゆるコミュニケーションツールは全て
are there in order to
strengthen that social nature.
この社会性を強化するためのものだ
Do you think the net
has the same effect, missy?
ネットにその効果あると思うか　お嬢ちゃん
Yes... I think it does.
ある…　と思います
I see... That sounds kinda interesting.
「ふーん　何だか面白そう」
Shall I give you a bit of assistance?
「ちょっと協力してあげようか」
What?
It's not a bad idea
「公安局の幹部候補に恩を売っておくのも悪くないじゃない」
to get a fast-track bureaucrat
in the MWPSB in my debt, right?
I see... That sounds kinda interesting.
「ふーん　何だか面白そう」
Shall I give you a bit of assistance?
「ちょっと協力してあげようか」
If "sorry" was enough,
then we wouldn't need the police, right?
「ごめんで済んだら警察はいらないんじゃない」
Man, I never should've
cooperated with the police.
「あーあ…本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった」
That's it.
こいつだ
Hm? What're you talking about?
何がですか
I never should've
cooperated with the police.
本当に警察なんかと手を組むんじゃなかった
Her choice of words is different.
言葉遣いが違う
First, she used "MWPSB", then "police."
最初は「公安局」 次は「警察」
Isn't that a coincidence?
偶然じゃないですか
Then, let's check as
many past logs as we can.
じゃ　手に入る限りの過去ログを洗ってみよう
MWPSB
Just as I thought...
やっぱりだ
Spooky Boogie rarely used
the word "police" in the past.
スプーキーブーギーは
過去ログでは「警察」という言葉はほとんど使ったことがない
The one you talked to this
morning is a different person.
けさお前が話したのは別人だ
The person we're after now is a murderer
今俺たちが追っているのは他人のアバターをのっとって成り済ます 殺人犯だ
who hijacks someone else's
avatar and pretends to be this avatar.
Our tracking showed that
逆探では 犯人はここからタリスマンのアバターを操作していた
the culprit was operating
the Talisman avatar from here.
This apartment.
この部屋だ
Door Breach.
ドアブリーチ
Hm?
Oh shit!
ヤッベ
It's bad news when I get a call from you.
お前から電話がかかってくるのは悪い兆候だ
Sorry about that. Some hunting
dogs got caught in the trap.
そりゃ申し訳ない
猟犬がわなに引っ掛かりましたよ
Finally...
とうとうか
I can get you as many replacement
proxy servers as you want,
代わりのプロクシサーバーはいくらでも用意しますけど
but do you still plan on continuing this?
まだ続けなさるんで
Of course. I have a duty to do it.
当然だ 俺にはその義務がある
Well, you are Mr. Makishima's favorite, so...
まっあんたは槙島さんのごひいきですからね
Please don't screw up, seriously...
うまくやってくださいよ　ホントに
Why are you guys not injured at all?
何でお前らは無傷なんだ
Hey, you don't
need to give us that dirty look.
いや　そんなにらまれても…
Maybe somebody hasn't been behaving well?
日ごろの行いじゃないですか
What is it?
どうした
We've got another victim.
It's that Spooky Boogie.
また１人ガイ者が出た
例のスプーキーブーギーだ
We looked for someone
from Inspector Tsunemori's class
常守監視官の同期生をさらに アフィリエイト収入で絞り込んで突き止めた
and narrowed it down to
people who had affiliate income.
Shoko Sugawara, twenty years old.
菅原昭子　二十歳
The murder occurred in her home
and was exactly like Hayama's case.
現場の自宅は葉山のときとまったく一緒だ
We found pieces of her body in the sewer
下水管から遺体の断片
and yet her avatar is still
wandering about on the net.
なのにアバターだけが ネットをうろつき回ってる
The estimated time of death is before dawn.
死亡推定時刻は今日未明
She must've gotten killed
after last night's raid on Exoset.
昨日のエグゾゼの出入りの後やられたな
Let's go back to the office and
rework our strategy with Karanomori.
戻って唐之杜と捜査の方針を立て直す
If this keeps up, we'll be
right in the palm of his hand.
このままじゃ　やつの手のひらで踊らされるだけだ
Dammit!
くそっ
Because of me... she got dragged into this.
私のせいで 彼女を巻き込んでしまって…
Missy...
お嬢ちゃん…
It was my fault.
私が悪いんです
Because of me...
私のせいで…
Did you use Spooky Boogie...
Shoko Sugawara, as a decoy?
お前は スプーキーブーギーを 菅原昭子をおとりにしたのか
No...
いえ…
Did you force her to cooperate?
協力を強制した
No...
いえ…
Did you leak information on her to the enemy?
彼女の情報を敵にもらした
No...
いえ…
Then what exactly is your fault?
じゃあ お前の落ち度はどこにある
That's... But she actually got...
それは…
でも　現に彼女は…
Yeah, if we had
caught the culprit last night,
ああ　ゆうべの時点で犯人を捕まえていたら
Shoko Sugawara didn't have to die.
菅原昭子は死なずに済んだ
The responsibility
for that lies with all of us.
俺たち全員の落ち度だ
For now, just think about fulfilling
your responsibilities. Let's catch this guy.
今はただ 責任を果たすことだけを考えろ
犯人を追うぞ
In short, that's the only thing we can
do to enable the victims to rest in peace.
つまるところ　ホトケの供養にはそれしかないんだよな
I found another weird case.
また１件 妙なのが見つかったよ
Melancholia's Rainy Blue.
メランコリア·レイニーブルー
８２歳のじいさんのものだったけど
It belongs to an eighty-two-year-old man,
but it turned out his grandson begged him
聞けば孫に頼み込まれて 名義だけ貸してたみたい
so he just let the
kid use his name and info.
And then, his grandson died
in an accident half a year ago.
で　この孫が実は半年前に事故死してるんだって
時任雄一くん　１４歳
Yuichi Tokitou. He was fourteen years old.
But, his avatar, Melancholia,
is still active even after his death.
ところが　彼のメランコリアは彼の死後も活動を続けてる
The grandfather doesn't even
know how to access social networks.
祖父はソーシャルネットのアクセス方法すら分からず
On top of that, he thought
the affiliate income was his pension.
アフィリエイトの入金も年金と勘違いしていたありさまだった
Rainy Blue is a big community, too.
レイニーブルーもすごい大手です
More and more ghost avatars keep cropping up...
増える増える　幽霊アバター
Is it even possible to operate several
different avatars at the same time?
別々のアバターを同時に幾つも操るなんて可能なのか
It's not uncommon for heavy users, right?
ヘビーユーザーなら珍しいことじゃないわよね
Yes.
What's abnormal here is
the acting abilities of this culprit.
むしろ異常なのはこの犯人の演技力です
Not only are these hijacked
avatars not incurring suspicion,
のっとられたアバター どれも怪しまれるどころか
they're more popular than
when their real owners operated them.
かえって本物だったころよりも人気者になってるんですよ
Why is it that tens of thousands
of users don't notice they're fake?
何千人何万人というユーザーが なぜ偽物に気付かない
Because it's not a matter of real or fake.
本物も偽物もないからさ
These avatars are idols
on the net. In other words, icons.
こいつらはネットのアイドル　偶像だ
Icons cannot exist
solely through their own will.
偶像ってのは本人の意思だけでは成立しない
Neither Hayama nor Sugawara
established their status on their own.
葉山も菅原も自分の力だけで地位を築いたわけじゃない
They were able to become
Talisman and Spooky Boogie
周囲のファンの幻想によって祭り上げられることにより
because their fans idolized them
based on their own distorted perceptions.
タリスマンやスプーキーブーギーになることができた
The idols' true feelings and their true colors
アイドルの本音や正体と
are not the same as the
ideals their character represents.
そのキャラクターとしての理想像とはイコールじゃない
It's not surprising that a fan could
do a better job than the real owners
本人よりむしろファンの方が
アイドルに期待されるロールプレイをよりうまく実演できたとしても
of playing the idol fans expect to see.
不思議じゃない
Are you saying that the
culprit is one of their fans?
犯人はこいつらのファンだと
Melancholia, Talisman, and Spooky Boogie.
メランコリア　タリスマン　スプーキーブーギー
He knows those three characters
very well and can imitate them perfectly.
この３つのキャラクターを完全に熟知し模倣することができた
The real culprit is someone whose
level of activity matches that enthusiasm.
それだけ熱を込めてファン活動をしていたやつが
本ボシだ
How can you find this person?
それをどう見分ける
Just how many people do you
think are fans of all three avatars?
３つのアバターに共通するファンというだけで
いったい何人いると思ってるんだ
We can use certain
criteria to narrow things down.
絞り込む条件はある
First, Talisman.
まずタリスマンだ
For the top one hundred fans among
the regulars in his CommuField,
彼のコミュフィールドの常連のうち
上位１００人について １日当たりの滞在時間をグラフにしてくれ
draw a graph of their
time spent there per day...
...predominantly around the estimated
time of Kimihiko Hayama's death.
葉山公彦の死亡推定時刻を重点的に
Around this time, the time spent in
the Field by the guests is altogether down.
この辺のゲストのフィールド滞在時間
何か軒並み落ち込んでるね
That's around when
Talisman's reputation went down.
タリスマンの評判が下落した時期ですからね
But then, after this day,
two months ago, it recovered.
それが２カ月前のこの日を境にして持ち直す
At that point, Hayama was killed
and Talisman was stolen by someone.
ここで葉山が殺され　タリスマンが誰かに奪われた
And yet, there are some
regulars who stopped coming
逆にこの時点でタリスマン·サルーンへの来場が途絶えた常連が何人かいる
to Talisman Saloon at that point.
This pattern on the graph is the key.
このグラフのパターンが鍵だ
When Yuichi Tokitou, who operated
Melancholia, died half a year ago,
メランコリアの時任雄一が死んだ半年前
and when Shoko Sugawara, Spooky Boogie,
died the day before yesterday,
そしてスプーキーブーギーの菅原昭子が死んだ一昨日
there should be a user
who showed the same pattern.
それと同じパターンを示したユーザーがいるはずだ
I see. That's the culprit's own avatar.
そうか  それが犯人の本来のアバター
That's right. Once the
culprit hijacked the victims' avatars,
そういうことだ
犯人は被害者のアバターをのっとった時点で
he no longer had to visit those
avatars' CommuFields as a guest.
それぞれが運営するコミュフィールドをゲストとして訪れる必要がなくなった
How is it? Did you find any applicable person?
どうだ　該当者はいるか
There's only one who perfectly fits those criteria.
ドンピシャのやつが１人だけ
Masatake Mido, twenty-seven years old.
Works at a virtual sports management company.
御堂将剛　２７歳
バーチャルスポーツ運営会社に勤務
His last Psycho-Pass Hue Check was
run four years ago at an annual checkup.
サイコパス色相チェックは４年前の定期健診が最後
After that, he didn't even
get caught by street scanners?
以後は街頭スキャナーに引っ掛かったことすらないのか
日ごろからスキャナーの設置場所を避けて通る工夫をするぐらいには
For his daily routine, he'd pick routes
that allow him to avoid street scanners.
That means he's got something to hide, huh?
後ろ暗い事情があるってことですね
Trace his access records.
こいつのアクセス記録を追跡
I've already done it.
もう済ませたわ
His last access was just a few minutes ago
最後のアクセスはほんの数分前
from a budget hotel in Roppongi, Minato Ward.
港区六本木のビジネスホテルから
His home address is...
Motoazabu, Minato Ward, the same ward.
自宅は同じく港区元麻布
Inspector Tsunemori, go investigate
the hotel room with Kogami and Masaoka.
常守監視官　狡噛と征陸を連れてホテルの部屋を調査だ
Okay!
はい
I'll go check his home in Motoazabu
with Kagari and Kunizuka.
俺は縢と六合塚とで元麻布の自宅を当たる
He's a dangerous guy
who's not only good at cracking
相手はクラッキング技術だけでなく
爆発物まで使いこなす危険なやつだ
but can also handle explosives.
Don't let your guard down.
気を引き締めて行け
What's that for?
何でそれを
Strong alcohol is the best
thing for handling illegal Holograms.
違法ホログラムの対策には強い酒が一番なのさ
That's a tip you learn after
you become twenty years old.
二十歳になってからの豆知識だな
MWPSB! Masatake Mido,
we demand you show us your Psycho-Pass!
公安局です！
御堂将剛 サイコパスの提示を要求します
Please come out!
出てきてください
これって…
This is...
Forget cracking Holo-Cosplay!
He can even crack interior Holo!
ホロコスどころか　内装ホロまでクラッキングしてやがる
コウ
Ko!
Wh-What do we do?
ど…どうすれば
Ko!
コウ
Crime Coefficient is 335.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
「犯罪係数　３３５」
「執行モード　リーサル·エリミネーター」
A pain inhibiting drug, huh?
痛覚遮断ドラッグか
With that wound, he can't escape.
あのケガなら逃げ切れない
Let's leave the rest to Ginoza and the others.
あとは宜野座たちに任せよう
Welcome back, Mido!
おかえりなさい　御堂君
Welcome back!
おかえり
Yeah...
I'm home.
ただいま
I'm okay.
僕なら平気だ
You guys are eternal.
君たちは永遠の存在なんだ
You were released from
the chains of a physical body
肉体の縛りから解放され
and polished by collective intelligence.
集合知によって磨き上げられた
You're the souls closest to Plato's "idea."
最もイデアに近い魂なんだ
No one can look down on you.
誰にも君たちをおとしめることなどできない
I won't let anyone destroy your nobility.
君たちの尊さを壊したりはさせない
I will... I will protect it at any cost.
僕が…
僕が　必ず守るから…
Thank you.
ありがとう
Thank you, Mido.
ありがとう　御堂君
Once I was guided by you.
かつて君たちに導かれた僕が
Now, together with you,
I will guide people and the world.
これからは君たちと共に
人々を…世界を導いていく
You are eternal.
君たちは永遠だ
But...
でもね　もうちょっとうまくできなかったかな
...couldn't you have done a better job, Mido?
御堂君　ねえ
Wait a sec. What on earth...
ちょっと 待って　いったい…
There's something that I've been
searching for... that I want to know.
僕はずっと探している
知りたいことがあるんだ
For that purpose, I did whatever it took.
そのためにはどんなことでもやってきた
Say, have you read Shuji Terayama?
ねえ君　寺山修司を読んだことは
Huh? T-Terayama?
て…　寺山
You should read his play,
Saraba, eiga yo.
読むといい　戯曲『さらば、映画よ』
It seems like everyone is an
agent for someone.
みんな誰かの代理人なんだそうだ
And further, those agents have their
avatars communicate in place of them.
代理人たちがさらにアバターを使って コミュニケーションを代理させている
Are you... Makishima?
あんた　槙島…
You have a thorough
knowledge of various avatars
あらゆるアバターの個性を熟知し
and imitate them perfectly.
完全に模倣する
You can become anyone,
何者にも成り得る君の個性とはどのようなものなのか
so I was very interested in
what your personality was like.
僕はとても興味があった
That's why I lent you
my people and my assistance.
だから人を貸した
力を貸した
あっ…や…やめろ
S-Stop it!
Give them back to me!
Don't speak in their voices!
返せ　その声でしゃべるな
But...
でもね…
I now see matters coming to a close.
そろそろ底が見えてきた
At least for the end,
instead of using a borrowed idea,
最後の幕引きくらい
借り物ではなく君ならではの趣向を凝らしてみてはどうだろう
why don't you come up with an
idea of your own to close the curtain?
You bastard... what're you...
貴様　何を…
You can play any character,
何者としても振る舞うことのできる君自身が結局のところは何者でもなかった
and yet, in the end, it turned
out that you yourself are nobody.
Your core personality is null. It's empty.
君の核となる個性は無だ　空っぽだ
You don't have a face of your own.
君には君としての顔がない
Since you lacked a face, you were
simply able to wear any kind of mask.
のっぺらぼうだからこそ
どのような仮面でもかぶることができたというだけだ
うるさい
Shut up! Stop it!
黙れ
It's about time to
say goodbye, Masatake Mido.
そろそろお別れだ　御堂将剛
The hunting dogs
that bring death have arrived.
死を運ぶ猟犬たちのお出ましだ
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
「執行モード　リーサル·エリミネーター」
Aim carefully and eliminate the target.
「慎重に照準を定め　対象を排除してください」
Clear.
クリア
No one else is here... right?
誰もいねえ…よな～？
Who on earth was he talking to?
いったい誰と話してたんだ
You did quite well this time.
今回 君はじゅうぶんよくやった
In the end, it was Mr. Kogami
who identified the culprit.
結局　犯人を突き止めたのは狡噛さんでした
To think that he grasped how the
culprit thought and foresaw things like that...
あんなふうに 犯人の思考を把握し予想するなんて…
That's how Enforcers are.
それが執行官だ
They can do that precisely because
犯罪者と同じ心理傾向を持っているからこそできることだ
they have the same
psychological tendency as criminals.
But...
でも…
Mr. Kogami comforted me...
and encouraged me.
狡噛さんは私のことを慰めてくれました 励ましてくれました
Even if he's a latent criminal,
あの人が潜在犯だとしても
it's hard to think that he has the same
mind as a homicidal maniac like Mido.
御堂みたいな殺人鬼と同じ心の持ち主だなんて 思えません
You're an Inspector. Simply fulfill
your duties as an Inspector.
監視官は監視官としての役目だけを果たせ
Draw a line between you and Enforcers.
執行官とは一線を引け
Is that an ironclad rule for this job?
それがこの仕事の鉄則 ですか
No, that's my rule of thumb.
いや　俺の経験則だ
What?
I once lost a partner who made a mistake.
かつて俺は過ちを犯した 相棒を失った
I couldn't stop him.
俺には彼を止められなかった
I don't want you to make the same mistake.
君に同じ轍を踏んでほしくない
This is a file from the Personnel Department.
人事課のファイルだ
Destroy it after you look it through.
目を通したら破棄しろ
Shinya Kogami. Enforcer. Male.
「狡噛慎也　執行官　男性　２８歳」
Twenty-eight years old. Former Inspector.
「元監視官」
What?
While investigating an unsolved case,
MWPSB Special Case 102,
「未解決事件」
「公安局　広域重要指定事件１０２の捜査中
his Crime Coefficient rapidly increased.
犯罪係数が　急激に上昇」
He prioritized the investigation
over therapy treatments.
「セラピーによる治療よりも 捜査の遂行を優先」
His Crime Coefficient
deviated from the regulation value
「犯罪係数が規定値を逸脱し　執行官に降格」
and he was demoted to Enforcer.
Looks like the fairy tale died a moment ago
In a hospital ward made of bricks,
I found it hard to sing
Red moon, come out on this foggy night
Now look at me, don't avert your gaze
I was born behind black iron bars
Wish for payback for the evil done
As you wish, I'll give you your justice
Before you destroy and get destroyed
Pay karma's price, and let's go together
Monster without a name
A world where humans' state of mind and the tendency of their
personalities can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations
are recorded and policed, these measured numbers
used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass."
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in the show
are fictitious and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.